<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Diego Castro | Pandora Box</title>
    <link>https://www.diegocastroviadero.com/en/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://www.diegocastroviadero.com/en/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.diegocastroviadero.com/img/logo.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://www.diegocastroviadero.com/en/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.diegocastroviadero.com/en/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.diegocastroviadero.com/en/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a software engineer with over 10 years of experience in the industry. In all these years I have gone through several companies in different roles and I have been able to develop myself professionally in different areas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This background includes working in large multinational consulting firms, where I have participated in various projects of different natures, I have been able to work on projects abroad integrating myself into different cultures, coordinate small development teams, accompany junior profiles in their beginnings, be part of projects with a multitude of teams and numerous, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have also had the opportunity to work in a startup practically from the moment of its inception, which allowed me to experience how difficult it is to create something from scratch. A very valuable experience that allowed me to see closely the other side of the coin, that of the entrepreneur.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am passionate about programming and I am a very curious person, which makes me be in a continuous learning process. This is what led me to study a master&#39;s degree in Data Science &amp;amp; Big Data. An exciting area, with much to say in the coming years and which I would like to be part of in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
